Yes, yes I started already in 2005.
I've done a little when there is time.
Which I rarely had.
Which all my friends know.
The car is an icon for me so it may take the time it takes.
I think it's fun to keep up.
-Hehris have you done everything yourself?
Yes, I ordered beams home and started making a frame.
Then I made a steel pipe chassis that I covered with sheet metal.
-Is the whole car a pipe frame building?
Yes it is.
Then you get the body and chassis as you want it.
If you were to buy a car and build on, it would be strange as the engine is at the back.
Then you have to buy a Toyota Mr2 or Pontiac Fiero but then the car will be completely wrong in the dimensions so it will be good.
It is difficult to find them because they are very rarely running.
-How many made Ferrari?
Ferrari made a little over 1100 cars but so people have crashed so you do not know how many are left.
-I see that you like the F40 because you have all kinds of toys in this cabinet.
I have been a few over the years and when you have found someone you have bought.
-And I kept stumbling on something on the floor.
Yes it is my granddaughter's car that she goes around in.
It was just a small MC battery in from the beginning.
So she was sad when the battery ran out.
We put in a 100 amp battery from a car so now she can drive all day if she wants to.
-I am completely mute and don't even know where to start.
-Where do you want us to start?
We can start on the inside.
-It's no car you just jump in and out. No not directly it is low and tight to get into.
It is very wide edge and high threshold.
In here, the frame is and it is a crash zone because there is nothing that receives on the page.
So it's a pipe system inside.
-You sit a little oblique with your legs.
Yes it is a bit like a Saab 900.
It is because of the front wheel is right here in front and so it was on the real car.
-Italen gorilla choir.
Yes exactly.
I've made my steering wheel straight instead.
The original is angled so it feels like you drive a bus.
This is a oscillate with a flat bottom so you can fit your legs underneath.
I think the steering wheel with a flat bottom is nicer.
I bought a Ferrari emblem and put in the middle.
I have chosen Sparco sprint chairs that I bought once in a while.
I think they fit well and the original also has red chairs.
I have used saber three -point belt.
However, not all pieces are in place.
Also has regular belts that are a requirement from the car testing.
A 6-speed box from an Audi TDI.
-Many people who build use TDI gearbox.
Yes exactly.
TDI gearbox can withstand much more turn from the engine.
It is a 01e gearbox from an Audi A4.
Curved sheet so it looks like an old -80s gear lever.
Volt, temp for cylinders & water temp.
Then there are ordinary gasoline champions, oil, speedometer and tachometer.
-What is it for buttons under the voltmet?
It is the fan and the heat.
It is electrical heat as there is no water element in the car.
Then you would have to pull a lot of hoses for which there is no room so it became electric instead.
-Should we check out here then?
Yes.
-What are you doing here?
I was not happy with the lights that sat here.
I rebuild so it should fit in and be nicer.
I had to remove the lids so I could change.
As you can see, it is a sheet metal.
When I cut off the lids, they got a little injured that had to be fixed.